

AVRAM STERN Full Stack Developer

O San José, Costa Rica

% (506) 8816-5476

SOCIAL

nastern9

in @stern9

ttps://stern9.dev/

PROFILE

More than 7 years of experience, working with different brands such as American Express, Delta, Kellog's, Dunkin Donuts, Playstation and others. Using agile methodologies on a daily basis for different projects. Fast learner looking forward to keep on acquiring new knowledge throughout my career.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree - ComputerScience

Ulacit

2016

Bachelor Degree - BusinessManagement

Universidad Interamericana 2011

High-School Degree

British School of Costa Rica 1994 - 2007

SKILLS

- 🕨 JavaScript🌆 🔹 React🏶
- NodeJS®
- HTML目
- Express
- CSS ■
- Unix**□**
- Git�

EXPERIENCE

Senior Creative Engineer

From 2018 to 2021 | Prodigious

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

Creative Engineer

From 2016 to 2018 | Prodigious

Delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

Associate Creative Engineer

From 2015 to 2016 | Prodigious

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

Media Operations Technology Analyst

From 2013 to 2015 | Bosz Digital/Prodigious

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

Provisioning SEO

From 2012 to 2013 | Local Splash

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

Manager

From 2009 to 2012 | Don Doner Restaurant

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

CERTIFICATES

- International Baccalaureate Diploma
- IGCSE Certificate

REFERENCES

Marketing Ops Manager

Tennessee Grimes

Phone: (773) 319-7070

Email: tennessee.grimes@gmail.com

QA Manager

Wendy Hidalgo

Phone: (506) 8701-5926

Email:

wendy.hidalgo@groupeconnect.com

LANGUAGES

- EnglishSp
 - Spanish
- French

INTERESTS

Music

Travel



Sports